[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Your life?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, never mind yours.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "never", "mind", "yours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "It would be good, though, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "good", ",", "though", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "I think it would have been a good idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "would", "have", "been", "a", "good", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "What do you want him to do to really show some fulfillment to that promise that we all felt?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "him", "to", "do", "to", "really", "show", "some", "fulfillment", "to", "that", "promise", "that", "we", "all", "felt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "ALDWIN: Well, I think that what I want him to do and what I think needs to be done are to some degree separate things but I do know that we've had a lot of programs, government-funded program for years now that represent both sides of the aisle.", "answer_tokens": ["ALDWIN", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "what", "I", "want", "him", "to", "do", "and", "what", "I", "think", "needs", "to", "be", "done", "are", "to", "some", "degree", "separate", "things", "but", "I", "do", "know", "that", "we", "'ve", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "programs", ",", "government-funded", "program", "for", "years", "now", "that", "represent", "both", "sides", "of", "the", "aisle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "That's not going to wash with the public, is it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "wash", "with", "the", "public", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "I don't think it is washing with the public.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "is", "washing", "with", "the", "public", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What is your view and should politicians led by the president be doing more to try to at least limit some form of weapon?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "and", "should", "politicians", "led", "by", "the", "president", "be", "doing", "more", "to", "try", "to", "at", "least", "limit", "some", "form", "of", "weapon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "MD", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "TO", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, I'm in favor of people owning guns but I'm in favor of there being the most arduous process for them to qualify to own that gun.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "in", "favor", "of", "people", "owning", "guns", "but", "I", "'m", "in", "favor", "of", "there", "being", "the", "most", "arduous", "process", "for", "them", "to", "qualify", "to", "own", "that", "gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJS", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "You don't think?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think at best it's 50-50 where there's a rural or semirural component or people who live in a city that's kind of a B-sized city and out West where they have access to rural countrysides and shooting and guns and hunting, that sort of thing, is part of the culture.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "at", "best", "it", "'s", "50-50", "where", "there", "'s", "a", "rural", "or", "semirural", "component", "or", "people", "who", "live", "in", "a", "city", "that", "'s", "kind", "of", "a", "B-sized", "city", "and", "out", "West", "where", "they", "have", "access", "to", "rural", "countrysides", "and", "shooting", "and", "guns", "and", "hunting", ",", "that", "sort", "of", "thing", ",", "is", "part", "of", "the", "culture", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Are you still flirting with it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "still", "flirting", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Well, because, first of all, I start with looking at the other candidates.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "start", "with", "looking", "at", "the", "other", "candidates", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Can your wife not read?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "your", "wife", "not", "read", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "She's certainly not younger, is she?", "question_tokens": ["She", "'s", "certainly", "not", "younger", ",", "is", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Condi, we are not doing this.", "answer_tokens": ["Condi", ",", "we", "are", "not", "doing", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["McDonald's"]}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Shopping?", "question_tokens": ["Shopping", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "That's him at McDonald's.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "him", "at", "McDonald", "'s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Is it good for any politician?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "good", "for", "any", "politician", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, I would imagine that the period -- the grieving period and the acceptance period when it doesn't go your way, especially when there was every inclination that it would go his way and remember what a long torturous, tedious primary period it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "imagine", "that", "the", "period", "--", "the", "grieving", "period", "and", "the", "acceptance", "period", "when", "it", "does", "n't", "go", "your", "way", ",", "especially", "when", "there", "was", "every", "inclination", "that", "it", "would", "go", "his", "way", "and", "remember", "what", "a", "long", "torturous", ",", "tedious", "primary", "period", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJR", ",", "VBG", ",", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Why do you have such conflict with them?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "have", "such", "conflict", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I don't think I really do have any conflict with them in the sense that -- that guy, you're talking about that photographer, I mean, I think the most important thing to remember is I did not punch the guy and the guy was overheard by witnesses going down the street going through his camera with his finger, going, yes, there's a one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "really", "do", "have", "any", "conflict", "with", "them", "in", "the", "sense", "that", "--", "that", "guy", ",", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "that", "photographer", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "to", "remember", "is", "I", "did", "not", "punch", "the", "guy", "and", "the", "guy", "was", "overheard", "by", "witnesses", "going", "down", "the", "street", "going", "through", "his", "camera", "with", "his", "finger", ",", "going", ",", "yes", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "If I could press the button tomorrow and flush them all down some swirling sewer vortex.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "press", "the", "button", "tomorrow", "and", "flush", "them", "all", "down", "some", "swirling", "sewer", "vortex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bing Crosby", "Dickens"]}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Did you bring any of your Schweaty balls for me?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "bring", "any", "of", "your", "Schweaty", "balls", "for", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Bing Crosby, Dickens.", "answer_tokens": ["Bing", "Crosby", ",", "Dickens", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Is it a fact that it's mainly live and it's dangerous, that' s it's -- you know?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "fact", "that", "it", "'s", "mainly", "live", "and", "it", "'s", "dangerous", ",", "that", "'", "s", "it", "'s", "--", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "''", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Well, there's things like that but that's the only place you can say it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "things", "like", "that", "but", "that", "'s", "the", "only", "place", "you", "can", "say", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What can you say about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "say", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, I think two things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "two", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBN", "JJR", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Am I gay?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "gay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "-- been more properly in love.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "been", "more", "properly", "in", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Are you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I may be unconsciously.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "may", "be", "unconsciously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Are you a naturally romantic man?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "naturally", "romantic", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I think I'm very romantic, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'m", "very", "romantic", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Or have you felt this before, but it just didn't work out?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "have", "you", "felt", "this", "before", ",", "but", "it", "just", "did", "n't", "work", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Well, I think as we get older, we have a more acute appreciation of that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "as", "we", "get", "older", ",", "we", "have", "a", "more", "acute", "appreciation", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Are you a nicer guy to be with?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "nicer", "guy", "to", "be", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "I think I'm --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'m", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "NN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Are you a better partner, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "better", "partner", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "I think the biggest thing I wanted changed is just how stress filled my life is, because I try to do a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "biggest", "thing", "I", "wanted", "changed", "is", "just", "how", "stress", "filled", "my", "life", "is", ",", "because", "I", "try", "to", "do", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Putting aside women and children, what's been the moment, if I could relive it for you, you'd go for?", "question_tokens": ["Putting", "aside", "women", "and", "children", ",", "what", "'s", "been", "the", "moment", ",", "if", "I", "could", "relive", "it", "for", "you", ",", "you", "'d", "go", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "I'd say it's probably a tie between my daughter being born.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", "it", "'s", "probably", "a", "tie", "between", "my", "daughter", "being", "born", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Is that what I said?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "I", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Other than women and children?", "question_tokens": ["Other", "than", "women", "and", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Now that I'm not TV anymore, will you still have me on your show?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "that", "I", "'m", "not", "TV", "anymore", ",", "will", "you", "still", "have", "me", "on", "your", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "I will.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "How do you even begin to cope?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "even", "begin", "to", "cope", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "You know, in the beginning you don't cope.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "in", "the", "beginning", "you", "do", "n't", "cope", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Is time, as people say so often in these situations, any kind of healer?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "time", ",", "as", "people", "say", "so", "often", "in", "these", "situations", ",", "any", "kind", "of", "healer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I think the only reason why time is a healer is because, you know, my whole life -- or not my whole life but certainly what felt like my whole life up to this point has really been about my girls and my children.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "only", "reason", "why", "time", "is", "a", "healer", "is", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "my", "whole", "life", "--", "or", "not", "my", "whole", "life", "but", "certainly", "what", "felt", "like", "my", "whole", "life", "up", "to", "this", "point", "has", "really", "been", "about", "my", "girls", "and", "my", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "How would you describe life before this happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "life", "before", "this", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "My life was fantastic.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "life", "was", "fantastic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "When you're beginning to realize that you can't get your girls or your parents out of this inferno, what was going through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "beginning", "to", "realize", "that", "you", "ca", "n't", "get", "your", "girls", "or", "your", "parents", "out", "of", "this", "inferno", ",", "what", "was", "going", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I mean, it's so horrific and so awful in that, you know, before this happened to me, I would never have imagined that there was anything that have could stopped me from going into a burning building and to save my children.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "so", "horrific", "and", "so", "awful", "in", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "before", "this", "happened", "to", "me", ",", "I", "would", "never", "have", "imagined", "that", "there", "was", "anything", "that", "have", "could", "stopped", "me", "from", "going", "into", "a", "burning", "building", "and", "to", "save", "my", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Did part of you just wish you died, too?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "part", "of", "you", "just", "wish", "you", "died", ",", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "Oh, god, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "god", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Do you blame anybody?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "blame", "anybody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "I mean, do you even really know exactly what happened?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "even", "really", "know", "exactly", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Because the house was demolished, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "the", "house", "was", "demolished", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Yes, that's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Do you have a satisfactory answer?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "satisfactory", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "He was an in store Santa Claus, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "an", "in", "store", "Santa", "Claus", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Yes, in his retirement.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "in", "his", "retirement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Santa Claus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Is that how you feel now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "how", "you", "feel", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121209pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "What will you do, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "you", "do", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "You know, every day has been awful.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "every", "day", "has", "been", "awful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]